[Music]
Do's mother provided these pictures to
the media confirming what public records
already show Rachel dollal is white damn
spok she's not just white she's Lowa
Linny
we by the way I just had my office
repainted in Lowa Linny we just she gave
up the life of a white woman to live the
life of a black woman okay do you you
know what a sacrifice that is Larry I
didn't think of it like that police go
looking for missing white women that's
true that's true Rachel doal is just the
tip of the incog Negro
Iceberg here's some footage I got of one
15 years
ago if she's doing good things for the
group are we mad at her I I could I
couldn't be mad at her until I found out
she was in
Spokane ain't no impression happening in
Spokane man had to import the black
people for the NAACP I will take nothing
and no one for granted it's nobody's
turn it's everybody's test and it's wide
open it's wide open that's what she said
yes yes well done
sir I want to this plate of chips right
now that's some good that's why Mexico's
taking over s of Dem was originally in
August all right August is too hot to
celebrate anything right so one year
they just it was just May 5th and said
hey mother let's just let's just start
drinking now boom sink of demise Donald
Trump announced he's running right yes
love
it uh first
thoughts my first thought yes if
somebody would hold a a sword I'd run at
it
hundreds of thousands of Haitians living
in the Dominican Republic now face being
Round Up in so-called welcome centers
and then deported that's right you're
going to be sent back to Haiti where
there are six beautiful houses waiting
for your arrival it was time to be
Puerto
[Applause]
[Music]
Rican you know even a chicken eating
Chihuahua on a cape started to make
sense I love Puerto
Rico Serena Williams has changed the
game she has
right I know it's very difficult to talk
right now because I'm just staring at
this at this man right here um I know
they're funions he's not going to kiss
you with onion bre I haven't I didn't
have anym I haven't I haven't had I
haven't okay
all right we don't know why he went into
a church but he didn't choose a bar he
didn't choose a basketball court didn't
choose a basketball
court man oh Oh you mean typically black
areas like basketball courts why didn't
he choose a recording studio I mean he
could have gone to a chitlin Farm I mean
break dancing class roller rings why
wasn't he had a watermelon stand why he
go there I yeah he could have and
literary Center could have been there
look if he went to Target a high
concentration of black people why didn't
he choose any prison in the United
States why didn't he do that huh it's
hard for me to take a governor seriously
when she says oh I don't understand what
would make somebody do this and then
your capitalist flying a symbol of
racism and separation and segregation I
think racism Trump's Nostalgia exactly
he was going to kill people whether he
had guns or not if he had the fashion of
bow and arrow he was going to do it he
hated black people see I I'm not sure
about I I I kind of take my chances with
a bow and arrow
hey America follow the nightly show with
Larry Wilmore on Twitter but don't
follow me home I want followers but I
don't want followers that's stalking